{
    "subject": "resource/Giorgos_Karagounis",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/S.L._Benfica",
    "human_readable": "Giorgos Karagounis played for S.L. Benfica.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8626297116279602,
            "question": "What position did Giorgos Karagounis play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8353330492973328,
            "question": "What is the full name of the football club Giorgos Karagounis played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8338797092437744,
            "question": "For which football club did Giorgos Karagounis play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7420240044593811,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Giorgos Karagounis's playing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972077488899231,
            "question": "Was Giorgos Karagounis a professional footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6851451992988586,
            "question": "Name any other famous footballers who played for S.L. Benfica."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5001113414764404,
            "question": "Did Giorgos Karagounis have a successful football career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.468885213136673,
            "question": "What are some of the major achievements of S.L. Benfica?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4644021689891815,
            "question": "In what country is S.L. Benfica located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4360332489013672,
            "question": "Is S.L. Benfica a Portuguese football club?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giorgos Karagounis played for S.L. Benfica.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1840_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country is S.L. Benfica located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1840_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the major achievements of S.L. Benfica?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1840_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Giorgos Karagounis have a successful football career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1840_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1840_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Giorgos Karagounis played for Inter Milan and Benfica, which suggests that he did play for S.L. Benfica."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Giorgos Karagounis played for Benfica during his club career."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}